Guide to the Wells Rich Greene Inc. Records, 1954-1998 and undated RL.01365
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1954-1998 and undated (Acc. 98-0396), 140 boxes
  - Video and Film
    - Westinghouse
      - Historical--27-43 spots (2 lists enclosed). Undated. TRT: 22:30 Plus (Box 114)
    - Multiple Client Reels & Agency Tapes (Box 115)
      - Misc. 10. TV Rental Advertising--Retail Uses of TV--11 clients (list enclosed--1. The Popular. 2. Foleys. 3. Belks. 4. Prangee. 5. Marshal Field. 6. J.L. Brandei's. 7. Fannins. 8. WohlShoe--Jacqueline. 9. Belk's Shoe Dept. 10. Murray Shoes. 11. May Company Hush Puppies.). Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 115)
      - Misc. 12. Bonanzas--C. Moss Presentation & 13 May Company spots. 1973. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 115)
      - Misc. 21. Braniff Airlines--2 spots-- Last of the Plain Planes & Airstrip; Underoos--1 spot--Mother. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 115)
      - Misc. 50. Rombex Film--5 spots--1. Hush Puppies. 2. Jones--Lost Art & Egg Break. 4. Westinghouse--Range. 5. Warners--Bra. 1976. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 115)
      - Agency Reel--1. Chase Manhattan Bank--Building :60. 2. Heineken--2 spots--Doggie & Me Too :60. 3. Toys R Us--2 spots :60. 4. Hertz--Covered Return :30. 5. Amstel--Zodiac :30. 6. Tag Heuer Success. It's a Mind Game :60. 1998. TRT: 5:00 (Box 115)
      - (List Enclosed) 1. Chase. 2. Sure. 3. Continental. 4. NYSE. 5. IBM. 6. Spectracide. 7. MCI. 8. Seagram. 9. Midas. 10. D& B. 11. AD. 12. Rawanda. 13. Olay. 14. Ford. 15. Sheraton. 16. MS. 17. Clairol. 18. Pringles. 19. Hertz. 20. Gain. 21. Heineken. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 115)
      - Agency Reel--1. Tag Heuer 2. Clairol 3. Pringles 4. Ford 5. Liberty Mutual 6. Ad Council 7. Caisse D'Epargne 8. BMW 9. Toy'R'Us 10. Hertz 11. Gain 12. Citgo 13. Heinekin 14. Gillette. 1997. TRT: 9:30 + (Box 115)
      - Agency Reel--1. Amstel. 2. Vagistat. 3. Pringle. 4. Gain. 5. Toys'R'Us. 6. Liberty Mutual. 7. Ad Council. 8. Rainforest Alliance. 9. Chase. 10 & 11. Heineken. Undated. TRT: Circa 5:30 (Box 115)
      - AR6. 1995 Creative--for TV--1. Chase. 2. Clair. l3. Ford. 4. Gain. 5. ITT Sheraton. 6. ITT Corporate. 7. Midas. 8. Mobil Land. 9. Children's Defense Fund. 10. MultipleSclerosis. 11. Oil of Olay. 12. Pringles. 13. Toys'R'Us. 14. United Industries. 15. Ad Council--for Radio--1. Chase. 2. Ad Council. 3. ITT Sheraton. 4. Midas. 5. TAG Heuer. 6. Mobil Land. 7. NYSE. 8. UJA. 9. Seagrams (list enclosed). 1995. TRT: Circa 42:45 (Box 115)
      - AR7. (1995?) --46 spots--B& H; Midas; AMC; Love; BIC; GleemScore; TWA; Tender Vittles; Alka Seltzer; Tic Tac; Sure Underoos; Jack in the Box; Coldsnap; Ford; Atari; Olypmus; New York State; Max factor; Liberty Mutual; Hefty; Spic & Span; ITT; Prell; Pan Am (list enclosed). Circa 1995. TRT: Circa 25:00 (Box 115)
      - AR8. (1995?) 16 spots-- Black Adder; Ford; Pringles; Toys'R'Us; Oil of Olay; ITT; Clairol Herbal Essence; Midas; Hertz; Ad Council; American Red Cross (list enclosed). Circa 1995. TRT: Circa 8:00 (Box 115)
      - AR9. Compilation of Commercials from June 1995-Jan. 1996 (list enclosed--about 50 spots). 1995. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 115)
      - AR9. Compilation of Commercials from June 1995-Jan. 1996 (Short Version) (list enclosed--about 50 spots). 1995. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 115)
      - AR10. 12/97--Wells BDDP Current Agency Reel December 1997 (list enclosed--17 spots) --Tag Heuer; Amstel; Oil of Olay; Pringles; Gain; Toys'R'Us; Hertz; Liberty Mutual; Ad Council; Heineken; Chase Manhattan Bank. 1997. TRT: Circa 9:00 (Box 115)
      - AR10. Assume duplicate of above. (Box 115)
      - AR11. Wells Rich Greene, BDDP Reel--Circa 19 spots--for TV-- Ford; Liberty Mutual; Chase; Clairol Hydrience; Oil of Olay; Heineken; Multiple Sclerosis; Toys'R'Us; Gain; Boost; Pringles; Citgo; Gillette-- for Radio--1) Heineken. 1997. TRT: 10:30 for TV (Box 115)
    - Agency Tapes (continued) (Box 116)
      - AR12. Agency Reel (For the Creatives) --16 spots--for TV-- ITT; Clairol Herbal Essences; Ford; Gain; Oil of Olay; Pringles; Toys'R'Us; Ad Council; American Red Cross--For radio--Citgo; Liberty Mutual. 1997. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 116)
      - AR13. Agency Reel (as of 7/21/97) --11 spots--Tag Heuer; Hertz; Liberty Mutual; Clairol; Pringles; Toys'R'Us; Chase; Ad Council; Oil of Olay; Heineken; Amstel. 1997. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 116)
      - AR14. 7/30/97 Wells BDDP Inc. Agency Reel 10 spots-- Pringles; Heineken; Amstel; Gain; Chase; Tag Heuer; Hertz; Vagistat. 1997. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 116)
      - AR15. [Current Agency Reel Nov 97--15 spots (list enclosed): Amstel; Oil of Olay; Pringles; Gain; Boost; Hertz; Liberty mutual; Chase Manhattan; Heineken. 1997. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 116)
      - WRG 1-A. Agency Cassette Reel #1 (list enclosed) --Sunoco; Hush Puppies; Jones; Safeguard; Westinghouse; Sure; Dog Chow; Tic Tac; Warner's; Alka Seltzer; Noxell; Bic; Prell; TWA. 1976. TRT: 12:00 (Box 116)
      - WRG 2. WRG Agency Videocassette #2 for Procter & Gamble Meeting 10/21/76 (list enclosed) --Sunoco; Ralston Purina; White Westinghouse; Warners; Jones Diary farms; Miles Labs; TWA. 1976. TRT: 12:00 (Box 116)
      - WRG 2A. (duplicate of above) (Box 116)
      - WRG 2A. (duplicate of above) (Box 116)
      - WRG 5. Agency Cassette--Reel #5 (list enclosed) --Sunoco; Wolverine; Jones Dairy Farm; Procter & Gamble; White Westinghouse; Ralston Purina; Ferraro; Warner's; Miles Labs; TWA. 1976. TRT: 13:35 (Box 116)
      - WRG 5. (duplicate of above) (Box 116)
      - WRG 6. Agency Cassette--Reel #6 (list enclosed) --Sunoco; Wolverine; Jones Dairy Farm; Procter & Gamble; White Westinghouse; Ralston Purina; Ferraro; Warner's; Miles Labs; TWA. 1976. TRT: 11:35 (Box 116)
      - WRG 8. Agency Reel #8--Citi-Bank Presentation 12/3/76 (list enclosed) (Procter & Gamble); BIC; Sunoco; Wolverine; Jones Dairy Farm; White Westinghouse; Ralston Purina; Ferraro Candy; Warner's; Miles Labs; TWA; Midas. 1976. TRT: 19:02 (Box 116)
      - WRG 8. (duplicate of above) (Box 116)
      - WRG 8. Agency Reel #8--Citi-Bank Presentation 12/3/76 (Corrected). 1976. TRT: 20:00 (Box 116)
      - WRG 9. C. Fredericks1/6/77 / use 2850 #3 Only WRG Screening Reel-- (list enclosed) --Midas; Ralston Purina; Miles; Sunoco; BIC; Westinghouse; TWA. 1977. TRT: Circa 7:30 (Box 116)
      - WRG 19. WRG Commercials Samples Fro 6/28/77--12/30/77--29spots (list enclosed). 1977. TRT: 15:00 or more (Box 116)
      - WRG 20. Agency Reel for 5/3--5/4/78: January 78 to April 7820 spots--Wolverine; BIC; Miles Labs; Union Underwear; TWA; Ferrero Candy; Procter & Gamble; US Magazine; Ralston Purina; Citibank; Savin Business Machines; Olympus; New York State Dept. Of Commerce. 1978. TRT: Circa 10:00 (Box 116)
    - Agency Tapes (continued) (Box 117)
      - WRG 21. Agency Sample Reel for Sony (no list). 1978. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 117)
      - WRG 22. WRG Agency Reel, Ad Age Presentation 8/78 Chicago-- B& H; AMC; TWA; Midas; Love; BIC; Sunoco; Alka Seltzer; Procter & Gamble; NYS. 1978. TRT: Circa 36:00 (Box 117)
      - WRG 23. Current Agency Reel for Jenos (list enclosed--11 spots) -- Pringles; BIC; Diners; Midas; Ford. 1979. TRT: 8:00 (Box 117)
      - WRG 24. Nikon EM--Best in You & Come Out Shooting. 1980. TRT: 1:00 (Box 117)
      - WRG 25. WRG Retrospective. Circa 1980. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 117)
      - WRG 25A. WRG Retrospective Master. 1980. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 117)
      - WRG 26. WRG Board Meeting Nov 80 (list enclosed) --33 spots-- New York State; Alka Seltzer; Savin; Tender Vittles; Chex; Dog Chow; BIC Shaver; Pringles; Olympus; Sunoco; Sure; Ford; Brittania; Jack-in-the Box; Braniff; Hills Brothers; Century 21; Continental Bank; Bonz; KVI Radio Station; Dallas Opera; Dad's; Chuck Wagon; Heath; Puppy Chow; Six Flags; Yellow Pages. 1980. TRT: 18:30 (Box 117)
      - WRG 27. Commercials Aired July 1 to Oct 1, 1980 (no list). 1980. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 117)
      - WRG 27A. TV Commercials on Air Between July 1, 1980 and October2, 1980 (no list). 1980. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 117)
      - WRG 28. History of Photography (slide show). 1981. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 117)
      - WRG 29. Agency Reel 1982-1982 (list enclosed) --Atari; Ford; Chase; Pan Am; Chex; Sunoco; New York State; Merit; Savin; Union; Tender Vittles; Pringles; Max Factor; Midas; Maxi; Safeguard; AS; Hills Brothers; BIC; Butcher's Blend; Jack-in-the-Box; Banner; Prell; Alka Seltzer; Century 21; Wolverine. 1982-1983. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 117)
      - WRG 30. The Best of Times--Baby Concept version & Baby short version. 1984. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 117)
      - WRG 31. Musical Commercials Montage. 1986. TRT: 2:14 (Box 117)
      - WRG 33. Introduction- Mary Calhoun Moss Presents: The Real Story. 1986. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 117)
      - WRG 34. Mary Calhoun Moss Presents: The Real Story short version. With flip revisions. 1986. TRT: 5:00 (Box 117)
      - WRG 37. Financial Services Reel--Citibank N/A & Chase Manhattan Bank N/A Master. 1986. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 117)
    - Agency Tapes (continued) (Box 118)
      - WRG 38. Introduction- Mary Calhoun Moss Presents II Master. 1986. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 118)
      - WRG 39. Mary Calhoun Moss Presents: Toys-In-House. 1986. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 118)
      - WRG 40. Mary Calhoun Moss Presents: The Real Story--In House. 1986. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 118)
      - WRG 45. Style Presentation Master. 1987. TRT: 2:14 (Box 118)
      - WRG 46. Benson Hedges--All Commercials Film Trf. 3/13/87. 1987. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 118)
      - WRG 47. Master Card Pitch 4//10/87. 1987. TRT: 10:12 (Box 118)
      - WRG 51. Products Logos--2 versions. 1990. TRT: Circa 1:00 (Box 118)
      - WRG 52. Sales Film--Delux Ultra Lights--16 Trf. 1990. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 118)
      - WRG 54. Party Reel A--41 spots (Repeater Reel). 1991. TRT: 75:00 (Box 118)
      - WRG 55. Party Reel B (Repeater Reel). 1991. TRT: 75:00 (Box 118)
      - WRG 56. French Press Conference Reel. 1991. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 118)
      - WRG 57. Press Reel--Wells, Rich, Greene Half. 1991. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 118)
      - WRG 58. Jean-Marie Dru and John Sharkey Speech. 1991. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 118)
      - WRG 59. BDDP International Selections (does not include Paris). Circa 1991. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 118)
      - WRG 61. Press Conference--French Half Reel C. 1991. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 118)
      - WRG 61A. probably same as above (Box 118)
    - Agency Tapes (continued) (Box 119)
      - WRG 62. The Birth --Rev 2/13/92. 1992. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 119)
      - WRG 63. The Way Walk-In Video with Music. Circa 1991. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 119)
      - WRG 63A. The Way Walk-In. 1991. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 119)
      - WRG 64. Chemical Manufacturers Assoc.--Responsible Care Master. 1992. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 119)
      - WRG 65. Bagir--Men's Clothing--New Business Presentation for Bagir / Israel. 1993. TRT: 27:58 (Box 119)
      - WRG 66. Sears Presentation 3 Master. 1993. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 119)
      - WRG 67. National Geographic--Bastoni Barnes, National Geographic Presentation. 1993. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 119)
      - WRG 68. Case History Reel for American Egg Board Master. 1993. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 119)
      - WRG 69. Nutsweet-- (Rip-o-matic) presentation--New World title ver. Van Halen Music. 1993. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 119)
      - WRG 70. Nutsweet-- (Rip-o-matic) --New World 3 version.Presentation. 1993. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 119)
      - WRG 72. Sears--New Business Pitch--Follow Up Video--Final. 1993. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 119)
      - WRG 73. Sears--7 spots; 8-brand store. 1993. TRT: Circa 4:00 (Box 119)
      - WRG 74. Sears Focus Group--2 spots. 1993. TRT: Circa 1:00 (Box 119)
      - WRG 75. Favya--New Business Presentation. 1993. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 119)
      - WRG 75A. Favya Presentation (different date). 1993. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 119)
      - WRG 76. (see box 123 with Public Service reels) (Box 119)
      - WRG 77A. Sears--New Business Pitch (Rip-o-matic Selects) Reel 1 of 4. 1993. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 119)
    - Agency Tapes (continued) (Box 120)
      - WRG 77B. Sears--New Business Pitch (Rip-o-matic Selects) Reel 2 of 4. 1993. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 120)
      - WRG 77C. Sears--New Business Pitch (Rip-o-matic Selects) Reel 3 of 4. 1993. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 120)
      - WRG 77D. Sears--New Business Pitch (Rip-o-matic Selects) Reel 4 of 4. 1993. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 120)
      - WRG 78. Sears New Business Pitch--Swipe Selects (Stills; requires ADO) 1 of 1 (list enclosed- 306 stills). 1993. TRT: 10:00 (Box 120)
      - WRG 79. New Business--Fayva--Street Viseo. Circa 1993. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 120)
      - WRG 79. Street Video--Fayva--Dave Accentta (possibly same as above) (duplicate of above). 1993. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 120)
      - WRG 80. Sears Presentation. 1993. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 120)
      - WRG 80A. Sears Presentation (duplicate or continuation of above). 1993. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 120)
      - WRG 81. Real People. 1993. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 120)
      - WRG 82. 3 spots--Motorcycle Fantasy, Runaway Fantasy, Lounge Singer Fantasy. 1993. TRT: 1:30 (Box 120)
      - WRG 83. Fayva Presentation Master. 1993. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 120)
      - WRG 84. Bastoni Barnes Research (Train Travel). Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 120)
      - WRG 85. Montgomery Ward. 1993. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 120)
      - WRG 87. Central American Coffee--Cafe Central (Rip-o-matic). Circa 1993. TRT: 1:00 (Box 120)
      - WRG 88. Airline Video with Charlie Moss (Delta Only). Circa 1993. TRT: 8:45 (Box 120)
    - Agency Tapes (continued) (Box 121)
      - WRG 89. Airline Video version II with Charlie Moss (Delta / United). Circa 1993. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 121)
      - WRG 90. New York Alliance. 1993. TRT: 3:16 (Box 121)
      - WRG 91. Phillips Reel. 1993. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 121)
      - WRG 92. TWA--Vox Pop--The Observatory. 1993. TRT: 2:10 (Box 121)
      - WRG 93. [Agency Creative Reel for TWA--Quo Vadis--13 spots-- Braniff; TWA; Pan Am; Pan Am Shuttle; Ford; Midas; IBM; Hertz. 1993. TRT: Over 6:30 (Box 121)
      - WRG 94. Radio Shack--Original Show Reel #1. Circa 1993. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 121)
      - WRG 95. Radio Shack--Creative Reel Rev. Circa 1993. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 121)
      - WRG 96. Alpha New Business Presentation Reel--12 spots--IBM; Dun & Bradstreet; Pringles; Ford; Oil of Olay; Chase; Tag Heuer; Midas; Sheraton; Liberty Mutual (list enclosed). 1993. TRT: Over 6:30 (Box 121)
      - WRG 97. New Biz--Sprint Questionnaire Reel. 1994. TRT: 10:00 (Box 121)
      - WRG 98. New Business--Drakes Dreaming (Cakes). 1993. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 121)
      - WRG 101. Agency Reel 1993--Agency Screening April 1993-- January 1994; also includes Best of BDDP (list enclosed) Ad Council; Chase Manhattan; Ford; Hertz; IBM; ITT Sheraton; Seagrams; Liberty Mutual; Midas; Multiple Sclerosis; Procter & Gamble (Gain, Pringles, Oil of Olay); Reckitt & Colman; United Industries; BNP; Tourtel Beer; UAP; Sugar. 1994. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 121)
      - WRG 102. Philips Agency Reel--16 spots--Pringles; Ford; Chase; Oil of Olay; Tag Heuer; Midas, Sheraton; Liberty Mutual; Dun & Bradstreet; IBM (list enclosed). 1994. TRT: Over 8:30 (Box 121)
      - WRG 103. New Business--Milk Board--Rip-o-matic for Milk Board Pitch (Wells' food experience). Circa 1994. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 121)
      - WRG 104. Sprint--Video Conferencing Rip-o-matic. Circa 1994. TRT: :30 (Box 121)
      - WRG 105. Sprint--2 spots. Circa 1994. TRT: 1:30 (Box 121)
      - WRG 106. Sprint--Maple Grove Direct Response Final. Circa 1994. TRT: :30 (Box 121)
    - Agency Tapes (continued) (Box 122)
      - WRG 107. Philip Morris--6 spots. 1994. TRT: 3:00 (Box 122)
      - WRG 108. New Business--China. 1994. TRT: :30 (Box 122)
      - WRG 109. Lennox--4 spots. 1994. TRT: Circa 2:00 (Box 122)
      - WRG 110. Sprint--Project Heartland Revised. 1994. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 122)
      - WRG 110A. [Sprint- Project Heartland Revised different date. 1994. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 122)
      - WRG 110B. Sprint Presentation Compilation Reel (old Vox pop). Circa 1994. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 122)
      - WRG 111. Sprint Presentation Reel--revised Jeremy. Circa 1994. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 122)
      - WRG 112. AAA Presentation. 1994. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 122)
      - WRG 112A. (duplicate of continuation of above). 1994. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 122)
      - WRG 113. AAA Vox Pop. Circa 1994. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 122)
      - WRG 115. Midas Case History for Ken Olshan. 1994. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 122)
      - WRG 116. Africare / Rawanda Relief--4 spots. 1994. TRT: Circa 2:00 (Box 122)
      - WRG 117. Crisis Coalition--Rawanda Relief Fund--3 spots Master (no credit titles). 1994. TRT: 6:45 (Box 122)
      - WRG 117A. Same as above with credit titles. 1994. TRT: 6:45 (Box 122)
      - WRG 118. American Red Cross--Rawanda Relief Fund--3 spots-Richard Gere, Vanessa Williams, Edie Brickell. 1994. TRT: 1:30 (Box 122)
      - WRG 121. Bloomberg Creative Pitch Master. 1994. TRT: 32:14 (Box 122)
    - Agency Tapes and Public Service (Box 123)
      - WRG 131. A New New York Statewide. 1993. TRT: 9:00 (Box 123)
      - WRG 132. AAR Video *Final*. 1995. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 123)
      - WRG 133. Chase Direct Radio--Imagine w Intro Tile for Agency reels. 1995. TRT: 1:00 (Box 123)
      - WRG 134. Bloomberg Business News--Frank Assuma Interview. 1996. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 123)
      - WRG 76. Aids Towns--Ad for Aids / Towns. Undated. TRT: :30 (Box 123)
      - . Crisis Coalition Press Release. 1994. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 123)
      - Misc. 71. Chase--Police Athletic League--3 spots. 1992. TRT: 1:00 (Box 123)
      - Misc. 77. Drug Free--PSA--Partnership for a Drug-Free American-- 4 spots (all Playground). 1994. TRT: 3:00 (Box 123)
      - Misc. 78. Drug Free--PSA--Partnership for a Drug-Free American-- 4 spots (all Playground) Master. 1994. TRT: 3:00 (Box 123)
      - Misc. 82. UJA Federation (United Jewish Appeal) --Keep the Fire Burning (don't let it die-version). 1994. TRT: 10:00 (Box 123)
      - . UJA Federation--Keep the Fire Burning (Thank you version). 1994. TRT: 10:00 (Box 123)
      - Misc. 84. Richie Havens Rawana Recording Session Master. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 123)
      - Misc. 85. Children's Defense Fund--4 spots (all Make It Big). 1995. TRT: 1:30 (Box 123)
      - Misc. 86. National Children's Defense Fund--6 spots (all Make It Big) --3 English, 3 Spanish. 1995. TRT: 1:50 (Box 123)
      - Misc. 88. The Door Massey/King Production. 1995. TRT: 12:00 (Box 123)
      - Take Our Daughters to Work Presentation Reel--Jean Wade Ringlaub (1904-1991), Shirley Polykoff (3 spots), Braniff: Last of the Plain Planes. 1994. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 123)
    - Agency Administrative Tapes and Public Service (Box 124)
      - Segment on Interview with Jim Smyth, Executive Director of CLIO Awards--Power Lunch. 1997. TRT: 9:20 (Box 124)
      - Image Advertising segment--Good Day Wake Up 5/24/95. 1995. TRT: 2:10 (Box 124)
      - Frank Assuma Prime Time Live. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 124)
      - Prime Time Live--5/28/97--Frank Assuma Interview about the Olson Twins. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 124)
      - Frank Assuma--Bloomberg Business News WNET TV (PBS) January 19, 1996 4:30. 1996. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 124)
      - Misc. 11. Mary Brubaker--Aubrey Franklin--Tea Sarono--KCCI- TV Des Moines, Iowa. 1976. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 124)
      - Interview with Jean-Marie Dru--Power Lunch 11/13/96, CNBC, 12:30 pm. 1996. TRT: 5:00 (Box 124)
      - Linda Kaplan Thaler--7 spots--Eastman Kodak; Clairol Nice'N Easy; Toys'R'Us; French's Mustard; Bell Atlantic; American Red Cross (list enclosed). 1997. TRT: Circa 5:15 (Box 124)
      - Mrs. Lawrence--Love. 1973. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 124)
      - Misc. 6. Telecom Research--5 spots (Procter & Gamble); Dog Chow; Red Barn. 1977. TRT: 3:30 (Box 124)
      - Misc. 7. M. Lawrence--Love. Undated. TRT: 5:00 (Box 124)
      - Misc. 9. New York Drug Abuse--Middle Class Rev. 1973. TRT: :30 (Box 124)
      - Misc. 19. CBS News--2/14/78 Good Morning America--Stan Dragoti & wife. 1978. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 124)
      - Misc. 54. M. Lawrence Print Presentation. 1982. TRT: 7:30 (Box 124)
      - Misc. 56. UJA (United Jewish Appeal) Federation--Campaign-- Delivering the Dream. 1984. TRT: 11:40 (Box 124)
      - Misc. 57. UJA (United Jewish Appeal) Federation--The Start of Something Wonderful. 1984. TRT: 60:00 (Box 124)
    - Agency Administrative Tapes and Best Of (Box 125)
      - Misc. 58. WRG Historical Reel--Jones; Locker Room; Ticket Agent; Dumb Shoe; Construction Worker; Magician; Chase; Gleem; Freakies; Everybody Likes It; Maaco--Joey--The Snake. 1985. TRT: 9:50 (Box 125)
      - Building. Undated. TRT: 3:15 (Box 125)
      - Here's Wells!--The WRG BDDP video (original wrap). Undated. TRT: Not indicated. VHS. (Box 125)
      - MTV News aired 9/1-2/ 94--Rwanda. 1994. TRT: Not indicated. VHS. (Box 125)
      - Late News 9/01/94. 1994. TRT: Not indicated. VHS. (Box 125)
      - Unidentified tape. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. VHS. (Box 125)
      - Executive Forum Demo Reel. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. VHS. (Box 125)
      - Advertising Age Best TV Commercials of 1989 (list enclosed). 1989. TRT: Circa 22:00 VHS. (Box 125)
      - Advertising Age--The Best TV Commercials of 1990 (no list). 1990. TRT: Not indicated. VHS. (Box 125)
      - The Best. Advertising Age The Best of 1991 (no list). 1991. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 125)
      - Advertising Age's 1992 The Best (no list). 1992. TRT: Not indicated. VHS. (Box 125)
      - Best Of. Best of 1988--Adweek Best Spots (list enclosed). 1988. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 125)
      - Best Of. Best of 1989--Adweek Best Spots (no list). 1989. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 125)
      - Best Of. Best of 1990--Adweek Best Spots (list enclosed). 1990. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 125)
      - Best Of. Best of 1991--Adweek Best Spots (no list). 1991. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 125)
      - Best Of. Best of 1992--Adweek Best Spots (no list). 1992. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 125)
    - BDDP (Box 126)
      - BDDP--Star Quality (no list). 1977. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 126)
      - BDDP 1. BDDP Paris--Selection of Latest Creative Work--8 spots-- BMW; McDonald; Caisse d'Epargne; Tag Heuer; Epson (Films in English or subtitled) (list enclosed). 1995. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 126, Video-cassette BDDP 1, Digital-materials RL01365-SET-0002, Video-file bddp_01.mov)
      - BDDP 2. Compilation Reel--18 spots (list enclosed). 1995. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 126)
      - BDDP 3. Batey Show reel Update- 19? Spots (list enclosed). Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 126)
      - BDDP 4. ARA/BDDP--14 spots--Moulinex; VVN; Red Cross; General Biscuits; Center Parcs (list enclosed). Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 126)
      - BDDP 5. Mancebo--Shopping Center Spots- Sogo--4 spots. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 126)
      - BDDP 6. Paris Selection of Latest Creative Work--Films in French-- 12 spots--Keno; Tatoo; McDonald's; Beli Crackers; Jockey; Danone Market; UAP Sante; UAP Johnny. 1995. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 126, Video-cassette BDDP 6, Digital-materials RL01365-SET-0002, Video-file bddp_06.mov)
      - BDDP 7. BDDP Agency Reel-- (list enclosed) France-Tag Heuer, Epson, BMW, McDonald's, Caisse d'Epargne, Beun, UAP, Virgin; Spain--Nenuco, Onda Cero; Italy--Aprilla; Holland--Center Parcs; Singapore--Sony, Mercedes; Portugal--UAP; India--Haywards; UK--Third World Debt, TV Licence. 1996. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 126, Video-cassette BDDP 7, Digital-materials RL01365-SET-0002, Video-file bddp_07.mov)